bananafever.com 2019-05-10

# BananaFever - 汝工作室 | Privacy Policy/Disclaimer

This website contains information, links, images and videos of sexually explicit material. If you are under the age of 21 OR if such material offends you OR if it’s illegal to view such material in your area please exit this site NOW.

We are a legitimate adult entertainment company founded in Los Angeles, California. We DO NOT sell our membership to viewers from countries like China or North Korea where adult content is illegal. Our payment gateway is blocked by those countries. LEAVE NOW if you are from those regions. You will NOT be granted access as member. Thank you for all your interest. We ONLY make our full version videos available on this site. If you see our full version videos anywhere else, they are ALL pirates. We DO NOT work with any other sites.

We currently have 3 Asian male talent volunteers. We are always open to get more Asian male talent volunteers. Please apply by emailing to info@bananafever.com. Please note that the male talent position is a **volunteer** position. It is an **UNPAID** position. Please also make sure you are an **American citizen** and live in **Southern California** before applying. Speaking Chinese or Korean fluently is preferred. Penis size **6.5″** above preferred. Fit physique preferred!

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on bananafever.com  The security of your Data is very important to bananafever.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.  This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 21 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet this criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

  * Personal Information:
  * Regular visitors can watch demo videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed. Howsoever the visitor’s IP address will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.
  * Premium Paid Members: Registration is required for paid members to access a number of other features including premium contents. The following personal information is requested at the time of registration: username (required), and email address (required). Additional personal information, such as year of birth, relationship status and sexual orientation may be added on a voluntary basis after registration, for members interested in identifying and potentially contacting other members meeting specific criteria. All this data with the exception of the email address and IP address becomes publicly accessible information.
  * Cookies: When you visit bananafever.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. Bananafever.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site’s features may not function properly.
  * Log File Information: When you visit bananafever.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.
  * Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

  * Your Personally identifiable information submitted to bananafever.com is used to provide to the user the website’s features and special personalized features.
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.
  * We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).
  * We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the bananafever.com user-experience.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen a password) which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.  Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Bananafever.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to bananafever.com and you do so at your own risk.
